There were seven girls on The Albatross
But it 's you who left this sadness in my head
You were seventeen when we were dating
It was in Augustów that I first laid eyes on you
Your name was Beata
It 's a beautiful name , my love
Help us come ashore
There 's no need to fear
We won 't eat you , my dear
Eat you , eat you ...
THE LURE
What are you doing ?
Hi there .
- What 's that smell ? - Beats me , boss . I got a cold .
Then stay home and don 't spread it around .
Mrs. Rockets , what 's that smell ?
We 're cooking in here , boss .
Actually they 're a friend 's kids .
And this is a nightclub
with a liquor license and adult entertainment .
And this room is for authorized staff only .
Beat it , you two .
Fine .
Excuse me , boss .
Here you go .
Take your clothes off .
Nothing .
Sit down .
Smooth as Barbie dolls .
This is great !
I have to say you really got me this time .
Are those real ?
Check for yourself .
Sure they won 't bite ?
They 're still young .
So what do you suggest ?
The slit in the tail ?
Where 's it supposed to be ?
There it is !
Thing is , they smell fishy .
It 's not that bad .
And if they dry out and change back ,
just splash some water on them .
No offense , but I was wondering ...
where 'd you learn to speak Polish ?
On the beach in Bulgaria .
That 's great .
Just great .
Give it up for Miss Muffet and " The Banana Song " !
Swinging in the sun
And thinking lazy thoughts
There 's a noise up in the sky
I slowly raise my eyes
I see a jet full of businesspeople
Packed to capacity
While down here there 's just a carefree song
And the lapping of the sea
It 's the banana song
It 'll be all right ...
I just splashed water on them . I didn 't hurt them .
Hold on .
- Breadstick ? - Please !
What are your names ?
- I 'm Golden . - And I 'm Silver .
" Imgolden , " " Andimsilver . "
Very nice .
They can do backup vocals and strip .
Here 's an advance .
Now get them something decent to wear .
I 'm new to the city
I wanted to put my best foot forward
Change what I can change and get their attention
A mention , a nod I could be soaring
But life 's gross and boring
I walk through the city Cars honking , polluting
New sights all around me
The lights , sounds , and faces never cease to astound me
Bright shiny neon
Is saying this is the best street to be on
Hustle and bustle Buses , people , and cars
So exciting we 're not leaving We like it here
The city will tell us what it is we lack
The city will tell us what is it we lack
We 've chosen to live here We want things to be clear
The city will tell us
What is it we lack
There 's not a dull minute Lots of people live in it
The tastes , smells , and pleasures
The garbage , the treasures
Pigeons and sirens Horns and pylons
Streets hot and exciting Parks cool and inviting
The city will tell us
What it is we lack
It knows for a fact what it is we lack
We 've chosen to live here
We want things to be clear
Hands made filthy by dirty deeds
Can 't stand to watch it go to seed
Want to hang out here a while before swimming to America ?
Sure .
Silver ...
what if you fall in love ?
Don 't be silly .
Would you eat him ?
Girls ...
I want you to cover up a bit when you 're singing .
Why that ?
Give ' em something to look forward to .
Remember : Give it 100 % ...
But not 200 % or 300 % .
- Knock ' em dead , Krysia . - Nervous , girls ?
Just have fun and let the rest happen .
Follow me .
Don 't touch me .
The next act is Figs ' n ' Dates ...
featuring two sisters ...
two little mermaids .
Let 's hear it for Silver and Golden !
Nice , huh ?
You were my heart 's beating
My life and spring so fleeting
My dreams before and after
My wind , my wine , my laughter
After midnight in my town the streetcars all get lost
The night is run by demons and the wires all get crossed
Infernal powers fiddle with the routes It 's all in limbo
And for some reason all the lines end up outside your window
You were my heart 's beating
My life and spring so fleeting
My dreams before and after
My wind , my wine , my laughter
Someone asked me how you are How 's it going
Someone with whom you 're at war Out there , longing
Someone rushes through the night on a streetcar
They think they know the score but I 'm already at your door
You were my heart 's beating
My life and spring so fleeting
My dreams before and after
My wind , my wine , my laughter
Girls ...
I 'm so proud of you .
My pretty girls .
Jesus ...
Where did you disappear to ?
Golden !
- Who me ? - No , Santa Claus .
It 's been a long time since I 've felt this lonesome
It can 't be the weather though it 's pretty loathsome
At night I get cravings that aren 't quite wholesome
It 's been a long time since I 've felt this lonesome
It can 't be the weather though it 's pretty loathsome
At night I get cravings that aren 't quite wholesome
Because I 'm sad and so are you
Now he 's sad ' cause we 're sad too
You 're all sad and they 're all sad
We 're all gloomy as hell
Bid farewell to cheerful smiles
Dark thoughts eat me up alive
I 'm a fly facing winter heavy , black , and sleepy
Because I 'm sad and so are you
Now he 's sad ' cause we 're sad too
You 're all sad and they 're all sad
We 're all gloomy as hell
Champagne .
Hey , Silver !
What the fuck ?
The name 's Golden . I 'll be right back .
You know I 'm hung up on you .
I love you ...
but don 't tell anyone .
Golden ?
Golden !
Open up , Golden . I give up .
You win .
Silver .
- Have you seen my sister ? - She didn 't come this way .
Have a smoke , child .
Go on .
I 've never smoked before .
That 's not good .
You want to have a pussy , huh ?
I 'm shaking all over .
" I 'm such a shy thing . "
You know it 'll make you lose your voice ?
I have to tell you something .
I really went crazy . You were amazing today .
I 'm the one who 's crazy .
Put it in .
Silver ...
You want me to be a girl ?
Don 't be angry ...
but to me you 'll always be a fish , an animal .
I can 't do this , as much as I 'd like to .
Darling Mietek ...
you 'll be the world 's first four-handed bass player .
Kiss me first .
Come watch over me closely
Follow my every movement
Take note of my tics and habits Memorize all my gestures
Be there at the right moment
Tell me when something seems false
Put your hand deep inside me and drag me onto the shore
If you do , I 'll convert
To a life not bound up with virtue
Regain my former composure
Learn all your secrets anew
Come watch over me closely
Follow my every movement
Take note of my tics and habits Memorize all my gestures
Be there at the right moment
Tell me when something seems false
Put your hand deep inside me and drag me onto the shore
And if there 's any time left
I 'll have another try
At catching you off guard
In any way I can
That which endures forever
Inscribed in our memories
There you are ! Come in .
Next you 'll be growing a tail !
Want some herring ?
It was a cow .
Good evening , ladies and gentlemen .
Mermaids make their way up from the abyss to the seabed .
Then they use it for leverage and swim to the surface .
I give you ... The Lure !
You come in and look me over
You 're picky and you 're choosy
They all want to be with you
Every day of the week
A wink like a fish scale flashing in the depths
So many albums we could have danced to
You choose a vowel A-A-A-A
I 'll have it played
Letters spinning quicker
Someone spiked our liquor
Let go for a second
Let love flow inside you
Discover the flavor of all that 's denied you
Holy moly
Bitter tastes can be delicious
So you 're lonely
Now I know that love is vicious
Holy moly
Bitter tastes can be delicious
So you 're lonely
Now I know that love is vicious
They promised frutti di mare
Now we 're feeling sorry
I 'm angry as hell
Picking at love 's cracked-up shells
One last piece of flesh
Lands on my plate
Charred like some scrap
No one wants to wrap
The head of entertainment .
I loved your act !
You were sensational !
The fiends are on the scene .
Don 't push your luck or you 'll get a broken arm .
You are my blood . I have horns under my flesh .
A fisherman broke this one off .
I tore this one out myself .
You 're so beautiful , and you have a great fish tail .
And an amazing voice .
Want to sing with my band ?
Keep an eye on her .
If she falls in love with a human and he marries someone else ...
she 'll turn into sea foam before the night is out .
Police .
Good evening .
What 's " police " ?
I can put the squeeze on you so hard you 'll gasp for breath .
You ate a citizen who was out on the town .
I know nothing about that .
I wasn 't born yesterday .
Leaves are falling like they 've gone crazy
Ravens are pecking at nuts
The wind raises goose bumps on the bare ankles
Of girls walking home from their classes
The wind feels freezing on my bare skin
I just need some warmth and comfort
Leaves are falling like they 've gone crazy
Ravens are pecking at nuts
My breath condenses in the storm of the senses
Anxiety tugs at my elbow
Frost and dampness are now in motion
Bodies swell with emotion
Leaves are falling like they 've gone crazy
Ravens are pecking at nuts
Oil on your palms Le ! me hold them
Babe , I 'll take you to Disneyland
We 'll watch Paris burn together
See fire spread in Rome
Or in me
You have your doubts about going out I had a talk with Daddy
He has no buts regarding sluts
So what if you blew your debut
Next time you 're bound to get lucky
Karma 's like that , it can dog you
The limelight tastes sour
You have your doubts about going out I had a talk with Daddy
He has no buts regarding sluts
Oil on your palms Le ! me hold them
Babe , I 'll take you to Disneyland
We 'll watch Paris burn together
See fire spread in Rome
How come you reek of fish ?
I ate some herring .
With your fingers ?
Krysia ...
Go and bone those fucking fish of yours !
I worry about you .
Stop it .
Nothing in the obituaries .
- Looking for someone in particular ? - You !
This one goes out from an admiring drummer to a semi-obscure singer .
Bill Chase with " Cronus . "
- I don 't believe this . - Stop it .
Good evening .
We open tonight 's program with an exceptional case
that occurred last week ,
when a Warsaw beach became the scene of a gruesome murder .
The victim 's throat was ripped open and his heart torn out .
Missing body parts have not been found .
Foxes and dogs have been ruled out .
Witnesses are asked to come forward .
The only tracks on the scene are of a human and something reptilian .
If any of our viewers has any information ,
please call our studios
at 43-10-53 ...
or contact your nearest police station ...
Fuck !
How come we never play volleyball together ?
We never roller-skate or ice-skate or ride scooters .
We can 't go to restaurants or bars .
We work , but we don 't get any money .
You 're still kids .
Kids can 't have everything they want .
- Brats . - Why ?
I 'll smack her , I swear .
One jellyfish , two jellyfishes
I wanna grow up and get all my wishes
Three jellyfishes , four jellybeanses
We want the plankton scrubbing our fins
Five jellyfishees , six jellyfishoos
Wanna walk on the water in my high-heeled shoes
Seven jellyfishes , eight jellybabies
Wanna drown in the water and stay dead for ages
Nine jellyfishoos , ten jellyfishus
Give me a boyfriend who isn 't amphibious !
Let go of him !
Leave him alone !
Poison
Inside you
That 's what the smell is
But is it done , is it done , is it done ?
It goes to your head
Noxious and nasty
But is it done , is it done , is it done ?
I can 't walk this one off
I need my glucose
My hair feels like viscose
The pain 's made me morose
But is it done , is it done , is it done ?
I want to apologize ...
for what happened before .
I 'm sorry .
Oh , we 're not mad .
Mind if I join you ?
Hi .
I 'll be getting real legs and a pussy .
You can have my tail if you want .
You want it ?
What for ?
I know you want a fish tail .
No , I don 't .
You can 't talk to him now .
He 's getting psyched up for the gig .
Are you a mermaid ?
We 'll just see .
The colors keep changing
From green to yellow to red
Someone who never existed walked out on me
I 'm getting up and falling
I 'm falling ! I 'm falling !
Don 't ask where I 'm going
Triton ! Triton ! Triton !
You were really ...
You need a lot of practice .
Triton said if you out off your tail , you 'll lose your voice .
Nothing happened to him , did it ?
Silver , you have to sing . We have to sing together .
That 's a superstition , you moron .
Try to stop me and you 'll never see me again .
Got that ?
It 's not my birthday .
What can I do for you ?
I 'm bound to the bed There 's bile in the drip
No veil , just a tube in my vein
I 'll be wheeled down the aisle in my surgical gown
As orderlies roll on their latex
The bedpan 's bright gold The dinner 's grown cold
And time flows like sweat off a midwife 's brow
I cheer myself up with bitter chocolate
Bitter chocolate makes me better
You can always choose to walk out
As long as you sign the release papers
On your own responsibility
Your own responsibility
You can always choose to walk out
As long as you sign the release papers
On your own responsibility
That 's for you , sis . To cheer you up .
So much smoke it makes my mouth dry
Bodies on the dance floor dancing by
Did I catch your eye on purpose ?
I 'm no rookie but I 'm nervous
Spilling smokes my hands are shaking
Is this the wrong step I 'm taking ?
As fatal as hara-kiri my emotions make me silly
Hearts ' magnetism pulls me in
Don 't want to fall in love again
Just one moment and I 'm reeling
You lit the fire of my feelings
On this dance floor I 'll dance for you
Cheat on you but still adore you
Hearts ' magnetism pulls me in
Don 't want to fall in love again
Boss ...
Silver could lip-synch . It 'd be great .
In my club ? Over my dead body .
Silver , don 't get me wrong .
Everyone loves you .
I love all of you . Lots .
This is hard for me , but everyone wants duos now .
We 'll have Golden go solo .
I don 't sing solo .
My whole band 's sick .
How are you holding up ? - Fit as a fiddle .
I like that song of yours " The Fly . "
That one 's by The Lure .
Let 's rock it a bit , huh ?
What do I play ?
Because I 'm sad and so are you
Now he 's sad ' cause we 're sad too
You 're all sad and they 're all sad
We 're all gloomy as hell
Because I 'm sad and so are you
Now he 's sad ' cause we 're sad too
You 're all sad and they 're all sad
We 're all gloomy as hell
Kiss , kiss , kiss !
Let 's hear it for the newlyweds ! Kiss !
The name of the band is Ballady I Romanse !
You have to eat him by daybreak .
Chickadee ...
He 's just a human . You 'll be sea foam if you don 't .
We 're not human . We 're just on vacation here .
You 'll vanish into thin air .
Give me this night
Just this one night
In warm houses people fret
All the stress , too much to cope
But here hands are holding hands
And in every glass there 's hope
We don 't need that much at all
Just to party till we weep
Surrounded by these spinning walls
And the rain of dancing lights
Enjoy the fun before it 's gone
Let 's get lost and forget again
All the times when we felt down
There 'll be time for all of that
When daylight comes around
Eat him .
What the fuck !
My fingers slowly ease their grip on your hand
The sludge of despair sinks to the bottom
One thing is certain
I 'll be warmer here than in your arms
I 'll be warmer amid these weeds and old car parts
Than on your knee
The undertow that drags me down
Is gentler than your hands and lips
One thing is certain
I 'll be warmer here than in your arms
Now that I 'm surrounded by creatures of the sea
Don 't pretend you 're sorry
' Cause I 'll be better off here
So much warmer here
Amid these old car parts
Than on your knee